## JEFFERY KIMBROW

Email: kimbrowjeff@gmail.com | Website: https://kimbrow-slice.github.io/JeffKimbrow/

Phone Number: (913)282-2500 | Location: Kansas City, MO

#### **Skills Summary**

Experience using RESTful web services, creating Full Stack Applications using Node.js. Experience with vanilla JavaScript, HTML5, CSS. As well as experience with vulnerability testing in the HackTheBox.eu and PG Play Labs. Working on Kali Linux, Windows, and macOS operating systems.

#### Education

### Degree / Date of Graduation

Currently enrolled in the *SkilledKC Technical Institute Software Development* program expected to graduate February 19<sup>th</sup>, 2021. As well as registered for the 90 days within the lab environment with the Offensive Security PWK OSCP exam.

### Experience

### **Employers**

Take out Specialist | Chipotle Mexican Grill LLC. | August 2015 – May 2016 |

Liaison between the customer and the front of the house. Cash handling, counting down the drawers as well as the safe at the end of the shift. Making sure that the customer satisfaction is met with orders being put on in a timely manner.

### Artist Helping the Homeless

House Manager | Artist Helping the Homeless | Oct 2020 - Present |

Manage and monitor overnight operations, Creating and filling out Excel spreadsheets, medication management, as well as case management, and statical collection of client demographics information.

# Volunteering

# Name of Organization

Volunteer | Artist Helping the Homeless | April 2020 – October 2020 |

Community liaison between clients and staff. Supervising clients overnight, as well as populating excel spreadsheets.